defaceherface.com 2015-10-17

# DefaceHerFace.com | Free Extreme Face Fucking Porn Videos -

### www.defaceherface.com Privacy Policy

www.defaceherface.com collect both personal and anonymous information on users in order to provide better services, features and targeted advertising to you. Your personal information will never be sold to or accessible by third parties. We will use the information we collect from all of our services to provide, maintain, protect and improve them, to develop new ones, and to protect www.defaceherface.com and our users. www.defaceherface.com will however fully comply with any and all court orders for user information on those users who attempt to use this service in any sort of illegal manners.

**www.defaceherface.com Collects Information in the following ways:**

  1. Information you give us. For example, many of our services require you to sign up for a www.defaceherface.com User Account. When you do, we'll ask for personal information, like your name, email address. Email must be confirmed ff you want to take full advantage of the sharing features offered. You are also encouraged to create a public profile.
  2. Information we get from your use of our services. We may collect information about the services that you use and how you use them, and interact with our ads and content. Info on user clicks on advertisements is anonymous.

The information collected includes: 

  * Media uploaded/Downloaded
  * Media Shared
  * Media Favorites
  * User Comments
  * Anonymous GeoIP info for Advertisement and language filtering

www.defaceherface.com will occasionally send communications with advertisements and offers from sponsors directly to your www.defaceherface.com user inbox, however your personal name, age, sex, location and email will never be shared or sold

**www.defaceherface.com will share the following information:**

  1. Contact information on 3rd party advertisers
  2. Legal Reasons

We will share personal information with companies, organizations or individuals outside of www.defaceherface.com if we have a good-faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of the information is reasonably necessary to: 

  * meet any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request. 
  * enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations.
  * detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.
  * protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of www.defaceherface.com, our users or the public as required or permitted by law.

###### Information security:

We work hard to protect www.defaceherface.com and our users from unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of information we hold. In particular: 

  * We review our information collection, storage and processing practices, including physical security measures, to guard against unauthorized access to systems.  

  * We restrict access to personal information to www.defaceherface.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to process it for us, and who are subject to strict contractual confidentiality obligations and may be disciplined or terminated if they fail to meet these obligations.

###### Dated January 1, 2013
